The Wolfpack is a documentary film directed by Crystal Moselle.
Locked away from society in an apartment on the Lower East Side of Manhattan, the Angulo
brothers learn about the outside world through the films that they watch.
Nicknamed ‘The Wolfpack’, the brothers spend their childhood reenacting their
favorite films using elaborate home-made props and costumes.
Their world is shaken up when one of the brothers
escapes and everything changes.
Self, played by Mukunda Angulo.
Self, played by Narayana Angulo.
Self, played by Susanne Angulo.
Self, played by Bhagavan Angulo.
Self, played by Jagadisa Angulo.
Self, played by Krsna Angulo.
The Wolfpack is a 2015 American documentary film directed by Crystal Moselle.
It is about the Angulo family, who homeschooled and raised their seven children (six boys and one girl) in
the confinement of their apartment on the Lower East Side of Manhattan in New York City.
The film premiered on January 25, 2015, at the Sundance
Film Festival, where it won the U.S.
Documentary Grand Jury Prize.
The film explores themes of sibling relationship, parent child
relationship, manhattan, new york city, woman director, confinement.